Pimp Bullies is a action, thriller, crime film
directed by Alfonso Rodríguez Zorrilla.
Five suspects holding a piece of the truth behind an unsolved crime.
Miguel, played by Ving Rhames.
Mr. watson, played by Steven Bauer.
Candy, played by Kristen Quintrall.
Monica, played by Chiquinquirá Delgado.
Isabel, played by Catalina Rodriguez.
Crystal, played by Lizbeth Santos.
Ichi the Killer (Japanese: 殺し屋１, romanized: Koroshiya Ichi, lit.
'Hitman One') is a 2001 Japanese yakuza splatter film directed by Takashi Miike,
written by Sakichi Sato, and starring Tadanobu Asano and Nao Omori.
Based on Hideo Yamamoto's manga series of the same name, its plot follows a psychologically damaged man who is manipulated into
assaulting or killing rival faction members of feuding yakuza gangs while being pursued by a sadomasochistic enforcer.
The film has garnered controversy due to its graphic depictions of violence
and cruelty and was subject to censorship in several countries.
The film explores themes of hitman, murder, prostitute mother.
The tone is intense.